Thank you for watching!
Good evening everyone, the morning chimes have sounded, and it's us, CJWICHIYUKU.
I'm Yuno Kunisaki, and I'll be your facilitator today.
It's the first time I've heard the morning chime, and it's almost always when there's three of us.
When it's just the three of us?
Yes. Mostly.
It was my first time there.
First time.
Yes, that's right.
The youngest person with the attendance number is the one who says that, right?
I'm very nervous.
Are you nervous?
This is your third consecutive appearance and third consecutive MC.
Oh, wow. Isn't it wonderful?
That's amazing.
I was surprised.
I guess that means it's well-received, right? Because it is.
Yes, it is.
I wonder if it's well received.
I'm thrilled every time.
It's amazing. You are always a great MC, aren't you?
You are a great MC.
Great MC.
It's like a mistake, isn't it?
That's great.
You've grown so much while I've been gone.
It's been 8 months, Mayuma.
Yes, it has. Because last October, ah, Happy New Year!
I am Riku Mayuma. Nice to meet you.
Hi.
It's been a long time.
What did you call it? Year-end reservation.
Well, well, well... Happy New Year.
I think it's better to say "Happy New Year" already.
I guess so. I guess you're right.
I'll say Happy New Year at the end of today's program.
Then I'll wish you a Happy New Year next time.
Yes, yes, yes. Maybe.
I might be on next time and the next time too.
Hmmm. Then again, maybe after the new year.
Yes. Then, let's begin.
Eh, Bichu's.
YUKAI, wait, before we do that, didn't Mr. Nonaka want to introduce himself?
Sorry.
Please introduce yourself.
Yes, I'm Nonaka, collection number 15. I am Kazami Nonaka, collection number 15. Pleased to meet you.
Yes. You have introduced yourself.
Yes. Thank you very much.
Let's begin.
This is Yuukai de Fufufuna Showroom in EBICHU.
Okay, thank you very much. Thank you very much for visiting the 47th Yubichu no Yuukai de Fufufuna Showroom today.
Thank you very much.
Our showroom is a sister showroom of Ubika-san's showroom.
It is a sister program.
Yes, yes.
Yes. Now, I will announce the ranking.
Okay.
Fifth place, Mr. Tamaro. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Fourth place, kiddos.
3rd place, kouhei hokkaido.
Thank you very much.
2nd place, monta-san.
1st place, tamamii.
Thank you very much.
You can get the original avatar of Ebichu Showroom by registering to the showroom and giving us a gift either for free or for a fee.
There are a lot of them.
Kaho wrote.
Free star gift or whatever.
Send a lot of them and make them all this.
Yes, I will.
Please click the twitter symbol at the bottom of the screen to spread the advertisement of this distribution on Twitter.
Please help us.
So this is the time to spread the word.
In order for as many people as possible to see this broadcast, I'm going to tweet an announcement on Twitter now, so please retweet it.
Please retweet.
What pose would you like?
I'll leave that up to the MC.
Because even now, when you read the tweet, you will be pausing all the time while saying it.
So let's do this.
Throw it or something.
This?
Then throw it.
That's unique. You're trying to get as many people as possible to give it a try.
What are you saying? What are you saying? I'm saying that in order to get this character, this original avatar, we need as many people as possible to give it away.
I'm saying that I want as many people as possible to see it by gifting it. Oh, I see. You said it twice because it's important.
OK OK, thank you. I said it twice because I didn't get the message.
They got the message. It was understood. If you want, the last explanation is understood. It's a sentence, so it's fine.
I'm glad, I'm glad, I'm glad. I'm going to talk about what's going on with this song right now. This song is playing right now, isn't it?
The new future sensation that's playing right now has been released, and it's this month's song. It's last month's song.
We released it last month. Yes, we have released it.
As this is the fourth in a series of 10 consecutive month releases, was there anything about the song when you were recording it, like this?
During recording? I wrote "Shin Mirai Sensation" for the album "Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku", right?
Kenta Alha, who wrote "Sayonara Himitsu Kichijo" for the album "Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku", wrote the music for this album,
The "Sayonara Secret Base" was conceptual, or in Kenta's mind and in Aluhaq's mind, various kinds of things,The time of "Good-bye Secret Base" was quite conceptual, or in Kenta's mind and in Al-Hak's mind, there were various kinds of stories,
The lyrics of the song "Shin Mirai Sensation" are very similar to the lyrics of the song "Ebisu next to you",
But as you can see in the lyrics of "New Future Sensation," there is a phrase "Ebisu next to you," and the lyrics are based on Ebisu, so it's true,
So, I was feeling very cheerful when I went to record the song.
So, if you listen to the song carefully, there are some emo rock parts, and the drums are rock,
I sang with that in mind.
I like the lyrics of this song a lot, and I like the lyrics a lot,
I really like the lyrics of the second chorus, "I'm still smiling and embracing after being hit by lightning for days on end," and I thought that was really nice,
I sang it with a cheerful feeling that I was going to move forward into the future, a bright future with a shining future.
I was so happy when I first heard that Kenta Aloha was going to write the song,
Yes, Yu no, I love "Sayonara Himitsu" too, right?
I love it so much, and now we have another song that I am looking forward to performing live.
Yes, it really is. When I was talking with Anaho during the recording stage, I was wondering how the song would turn out,
We talked about what kind of song it was going to be,
We talked about how it would be interesting if the two of us sang together,
There are a lot of parts that are sung by the two of you, aren't there?
Yes, there are a lot.
So, this song has not been choreographed yet.
I can't imagine how the two of us will sing together, so I'm looking forward to it.
Will they be at both ends, or will they sing close together?
I'm looking forward to it.
That's great, I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
What do you think? What do you think of this new future sensation?
What do you think?
There are a lot of people listening to it, aren't there?
You were also involved in the Rai Music campaign.
Yes, that's right.
What do you think? We get a lot of comments.
They like our view of the world a lot.
I'm glad.
It certainly has a sparkling, above-the-sky feel to it.
I can see that. Like the area where the water is flowing right now.
Light blue and pink and purple,
It's like a fairy tale.
So it's a fairy tale image. The current Akari.
The interplay between the members will be one of the highlights of the show.
Yes, that's true.
That's for sure.
That's true.
As I said before, I'm not sure how the part where they sing together will turn out.
I heard you're going to listen to the melody of the chorus.
I'm glad.
I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
We'll be releasing another song every month,
I wonder if the July song will be released in the near future.
We've already recorded it.
We have already recorded it.
I've already heard it completed.
I am looking forward to it.
I wonder what they will think. It's crazy.
I don't think so every time. I especially thought about this song.
And the shimirai sensation, too.
The lyrics "Ebichu next to you" is "Ebichu" in kanji.
Big.
But we are in katakana.
I was talking about that with Aloha-kun.
We decided to do it on a dare.
We have a certain view of the world in the lyrics, so we decided to use kanji for EBICHU.
I hope everyone will listen to it.
I am very excited about next month's song,
I am looking forward to it.
It's going to be tough.
I've already told Inokuchi to slide.
I'm not going to let him slide.
Absolutely not.
I've had him slide in the showroom, but he's opening a store with me.
Spoilers, you know.
Dare I say Kanji characters?
There is no lyric card yet. It's a distribution.
Oh, I see.
That's right. Because it is distributed. So I don't think everyone knows the song assignments.
It's an ear copy.
There are a lot of songs with two members, aren't there?
Yes, yes. I don't think they would understand it even if they compared it.
Especially since there are 9 members.
Did you shoot a swimsuit music video? I was wondering if you have done any swimsuit music videos.
Mire-chan, me and Fujii-san shot one the other day.
Oh, you did?
No, we didn't.
We didn't shoot it.
You did?
We were talking and Ms. Fujii said she would love to shoot a swimsuit music video.
I told him that Mire-chan and I would absolutely hate it.
Hey, thanks for that. I absolutely hate it.
I really don't want to do it.
I'll be completely blacked out with mosaic.
They are so quick to tell me to wear a bathing suit, or what, or if I show my belly, it's because I'm influenced by Cocona.
What is it with them, really?
But Cocona hasn't shown her belly recently, has she?
Not even in the costumes for the spring tour.
It's true that she hasn't been showing her belly recently.
You said you wanted to show your belly.
It's going to be summer again from now on. I may show it a lot.
I think a swimsuit music video of the principal would be better.
Well, let's start with a corner like this.
I'll start with a funny and humorous look back at the tour.
The first leg of the Sirity Wish Actens Anniversary Tour 2022 Drawer was completed the day before yesterday.The first leg of the Sirity Wishes Actens Anniversary Tour 2022 Drawer was completed the day before yesterday.
Today, we will talk a lot about the impressions and behind-the-scenes stories.
Let's start.
Yes, we have started.
On April 29th, the first day of the tour, we started our first tour in Niigata at Niigata Terrsa.
Actually, the first day was at JCOMM Hall Hachioji, and the next day was TDC, but it was postponed, so we started the tour.
So, it was the first time for us to perform in Niigata. I think it was the first time for us to be in Niigata.
I think it was the first day in Niigata.
I've been rehashing the event in a very tight schedule, and I didn't think it would be in Niigata.
I was looking forward to Niigata, catering and all.
But I was so nervous that I couldn't eat much.
That's for sure.
I did eat a lot after the concert.
Yes, yes, yes.
I heard that you had to travel to Niigata because of the change of the first day.
I know there are people like that.
Isn't it the first time for you two? Niigata.
Yes, it was.
How was it?
Well, they served hegi soba (buckwheat noodles),
I had it for the first time when it was catered,
I never really liked soba before,
Until now?
It was so delicious that Hinata and I ate it all the time.
It was quite a lot of food.
Yes, I just couldn't stop eating it.
I thought, "Oh no, I can't do the show if I eat this much," so I stopped,
But it was really delicious. But it was really good.
It was great.
Niigata's catering is always great,
What did Yu eat? Niigata.
What did he eat in Niigata?
Some kind of yogurt?
We also had strawberries. Strawberries.
Echigohime.
And something about this size, what was it?
Not bread,
Poppoyaki?
Yes, poppoyaki.
I ate a lot of poppoyaki.
Poppoyaki is very similar to Chenmin, isn't it? Taste.
How many?
It's not an Okinawan crepe, but it's very similar to the brown sugar Chen Min.
It has a very gentle taste.
It's delicious.
I love ebichu, so he always buys it for me.
I was really happy, it was fun.
The second performance was on May 5 at the Osaka International Convention Center Main Hall,
It was also the one-year anniversary of your joining the group and the 10th anniversary of EBITCHU.
How was it?
It was your first year since joining the group,
Me?
It was me.
I don't know, I felt that it was very fast,
It was really a memorable year for me, the first year of my 10th anniversary,
Riko was not there, so I was a little worried,
But I was really fired up that day so that I could give it my all,
After the event, there was a cake,
It was delicious, so delicious.
The cake was so cute.
He brought it himself,
He brought the satellite himself during the concert,
He brought it himself and quickly took a picture of it and brought it back.
He had it decorated with many colorful colors of the band members,
Afterwards, everyone, including the staff, ate a lot of cake.
Yes, we did eat a lot.
I feel like every year on May 5,
Not really every year,
I spend most of the time in Osaka,
As Akira-san wrote, he was not angry with me this time,
As Akira-san wrote that he was not angry this time, the previous time he was angry and had prepared a surprise cake for me,
But he had prepared a surprise cake for me after the rehearsal, and I was supposed to surprise him with it after the rehearsal,
But that didn't happen.
The cake was sadly put out in the hallway,
But we were able to do it on stage,
I felt so happy to be able to eat it with everyone.
But you all know Hiro on the tour,
I didn't do it at this time,
On May 5, "Youth Zombies" will be released,
I'm sure you came to the venue listening to the songs,
We are also on the second day of the tour,
We also felt like we wanted to make it even better since it was the second day of the tour,
It was a very enjoyable show.
It turned out to be a great Osaka.
We also announced new members,
And auditions for new members.
That's right.
There were many announcements.
There were many events.
A lot.
How was Yuna?
Yuna was so preoccupied with the announcement of the audition for new members later on,
I wondered what everyone would think.
I was really nervous.
I was so nervous.
I was so nervous, even right before I left.
That's right.
I was nervous the whole time.
Everyone was so surprised.
We were all surprised to see how nervous everyone was,That tension, something we are six of us,
At the beginning of the year, that's how I felt when the three of us were in the chorus,
It was like the second time in a year.
So it was like the second time in a year.
But now that the three of us were in the chorus, I could see the faces of the audience,
I could see more emotion in the audience's faces than I had imagined,
I could see more emotions than I had imagined,
I could see a lot more emotions in the audience's faces than I had imagined, but I was surprised to see that some of them were surprised,
I was surprised, but some of them also understood what I was talking about,
It was a very strange feeling. Osaka is a great place.
I am looking forward to seeing you again in the future, as we continue to improve Ebiji.
I am looking forward to it. I wonder what kind of children will join us.
Next, Hokkaido will be held on May 14 at the Sapporo City Education and Culture Hall,
I was going to say that I ate penance in Hokkaido, but I said I ate penance.
I still get teased about it a lot.
I get teased a lot.
They also tease me at storytelling sessions.
They say it was delicious.
Even if I tell them it was delicious.
It was delicious. It's not a confession.
After you went to Hokkaido and came back, didn't you feel that it was hot in Tokyo?
It was kind of dry.
They say you shouldn't eat in Hokkaido,
I was dressed a little warmer than I thought I should be in Hokkaido, and it was really hot in Tokyo.
It was hot.
It was not as cold as I thought it would be.
Not as cold as I thought it would be.
I was mostly at hotels and venues, so I didn't have a chance to go outside that much.
Yes, that was true. That's true.
Hokkaido is sometimes a difficult place to do Soul D'art,
I was very happy to be able to go to Hokkaido with 9 people for this Soul Art event.
Hokkaido was a lot of fun.
The next one will be in Ibaraki Prefecture on May 21.
We performed at Hirozawa City Hall for Coconner's outing live.
That's when Coconar was really nervous.
He was nervous, wasn't he?
He was so nervous.
He was walking around all the time, sobbing.
He was so cute. He was so cute.
You seem to be having fun. During the concert.
He seemed to be having a lot of fun.
I'm going to say this since the first song was at the end of the tour,
The first song was "All-out Runner," wasn't it?
Before the streets started to get excited, we were holding hands while everyone was going around in a circle,
The "kokonar" is a word that means "to connect and go around,
And there, both of us had a big jawline.
What? What?
They make funny faces because they are so nervous.
And then they turn their heads back.
Oh, my gosh.
I did my best.
You work fast.
It's amazing.
You must get really nervous right after coming out during this song, right?
I certainly do.
I get nervous.
That's why I got all squawky.
We were both relaxing each other's nerves with our pouting.
We made funny faces.
Make funny faces.
For this song?
I did that to this song, and even though I was holding hands with Coconner, we were going around in circles,
So we were relieving each other's tension.
It's the interlude, isn't it?
I think it's the interlude or the fall melody,
The D melody or the D melody.
Around the waterfowl.
That's right.
Even in that one, it turns, you know,
You can see their faces.
Just for the moment when we are all connected like this.
Just for a moment.
I don't think anyone has found us yet.
Maybe there are people who have found them. Maybe.
No one has found it. You know about the temporary contract, don't you?
The temporary contract is not a funny face.
The tentative contract is just staring at Coconner.
Is it simply a funny face? Maybe now.
That's a swear word.
Did he say something bad about me?
Did he just say something bad about you? Right now.
Yes, they are.
I thought maybe you could find your own way to relieve the tension.
Do you have a way to relieve tension?
No, I can't. When I get nervous, I get nervous. When I am nervous, I am nervous.
I don't relax.
I'm in a hurry. I think it's best to stay calm and not be in a hurry.
You are the most nervous, aren't you?
I get nervous too, and I'm in a great hurry,
So I take a deep breath, a deep belly breath, a very deep breath,
I take a deep breath, belly, a very deep breath, and look at all the upper leg tips all the way from the side,
I take one more deep breath and fix it.
Did you do something weird? In the spring tour.
I was able to loosen up inside myself.
You can do it, can't you?
I think I can relax by making funny faces now.
I make funny faces now, and just before I go out on stage, I have Hinata slap me on the back as hard as she can before she does the evichu,
He slaps me really hard, but it's not enough,
I want it to be tingling all the way through another song or two,
But he puts a lot of effort into it.
So we decided to have Hinata hit twice as hard as she could.So I decided to ask Hinata-chan to hit it twice with more force because I thought that was impossible.
Throughout this tour.
I think it's good to be tingling.
It's just right to be tingly,
Didn't it feel like you were listening to an idol?
I thought I was listening to a martial artist.
I was so surprised.
Are you going to get a bruise or something? Are you okay?
You can't see my back, so I'm fine.
Yes, you're right. My back is shallow.
I was the first one to fail in the belly-butt.
But you know, COCO-NA also has a routine of tapping on the back.
You have Mirei slap it for you, don't you?
When Mirei is not around, it's me,
COCO-NA also tells me to hit harder.
Both of us, the two AB types.
I see, so there are only two AB types and COCO-NA?
It's amazing how they put their energy into it, or rather, how they put their energy into it.
If I don't go out when I'm still tingling with energy, I get more nervous.
It's a little bit painful. So you drown it out.
That's one way to do it.
I used to pound the floor every time.
I do it every time.
I'm glad you like it.
So you don't fall down.
I also pat the floor during rehearsals.
It's not unique.
Wow.
I mean, since about Ibaraki, right?
The songs have been changed since Ibaraki?
Huh? Shooting star.
The shooting star changed in Hokkaido.
We changed it little by little.
Let me tell you about this tour first,
The setlist was composed of AB.
Actually.
A is goodbye secret base, B is goodbye secret base, C is goodbye secret base, and D is goodbye secret base,
A is "Good-bye Secret Base,
Sugagraze,
Sayuki Uchiba.
B is,
Tokimekiteki Tekkai-ron,
Kurun, shooting star.
Thank you very much.
But, you know, actually, it's because of the choreography.
But, you know, actually, it had to do with the choreography and so on,
I couldn't do AB well.
So, I changed it a little bit in the first half,
From around Ibaraki,
So, we did it.
That's why,
The hourglass of the universe has just turned into a shooting star,
I think it just turned into a shooting star.
The third song was "Ume" (plum),
The third song was "Plum Blossom,
The third song was "Plum" and then it changed to "Adults Don't Understand" and so on,
The third song was "Plum," but it was changed to "Grown-ups Don't Understand.
Yes, that's right.
And on May 28,
May 28th at Kalia Sogo Bunka Center in Aichi, Japan,
It will be my "Gaiten" live concert.
Is it really different from the other concerts?
Yes, very different.
It's different, a lot different,
You can go back to your house after the show,
There?
There.
Also, the atmosphere was very different.
The smell.
The smell of the outside was amazing.
I was outside all the time.
Indeed, the backstage area was just like a dressing room with open windows,
Yu opened the window of the dressing room,
I was sitting on a helicopter,
He was sitting! I was sitting!
He was holding me a little bit,
He was holding me, and he was holding me, and..,
I'm twilight, all the time.
I'm not twilight.
No, I was twilight, pretty much.
I thought so very much.
I was twilighted a lot.
I thought you were in the Yuuno-san mode,
I wondered if it was different.
It was an outside battle, so it was already over,
The next day was Hama Fest, so I had to go home,
I had to go home,
I had to go back home, so I smelled a lot more.
Mr. Frontalou wrote that he could feel Yu no Pi's nervousness,
Do you get nervous when you go to an outside concert?
No, I was not nervous, but excited.
I was excited, too.
Coconan, yes, I was nervous.
Of course I was nervous,
I was nervous, of course, but I was also nervous that my friends would be there to see me,
I had asked them to come,
I wanted to show them that I was doing my best in Ebbichi,
In that sense, I was a little nervous.
I see.I see.
Did you get any compliments?
I said it was great.
I was happy.
That makes me happy, too.
And the next one is on June 3 at JCom Hall Hachioji in Tokyo,
I was able to come back to Hachioji.
It was great to come back with nine members.
If we had done it on the first day, it would have been,
If we had done it on the first day, we wouldn't have been able to get all nine of us together,
So I am glad that we were able to make it.
Unfortunately, it was a weekday, so I know there were some people who could not come to see the show,
But I'm really glad that we were able to get all nine of us together,
I am really glad that we were able to get all nine of us together.
I am glad.
Hachioji, was it A or B?
B, huh?
I'm so excited.
I thought a lot about the meaning of the lyrics of Kirun with Aya-chan.
That's right. After rehearsal with Aya-chan,
I was thinking about the meaning of the lyrics of Kirun,
That was the day we talked while thinking about it a lot.
That's great.
It's great.
It flowed.
So fast.
What did you two make of it?
I don't know.
It's not just love.
Aya met him at a club,
And then you met Tsukihi,
Aya's a very cool girl, isn't she?
You're the cool type.
You're the cool type, right?
I try to be mature and appeal to him,
But I told him that my voice is not enough.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yu is a mirror ball?
Yes, a sparkling mirror ball.
It's a moonlit mirror ball,
I thought it was a sparkling place with no ceiling.
It's like a live music club or a club.
You were thinking about that earlier.
And after that, I was thinking about the weekend theory of crushes,
I want to fall in love, I want to fall in love.
Then, the setlist was like a real love mode.
And then after that, "Love for Rent.
We were thinking about the connection.
We were talking about the connection.
It was nice to have something like that.
It was fun.
Aya seemed to be having a lot of fun.
I like Aya-chan.
That kind of talk.
That kind of thing.
After the last stop in the love mode,
It's the Saitama Kawaguchi Sogo Bunka Center Lilia Main Hall on June 10th.
Saitama is Kaho's outside line.
Kaho-chan is on the outside line.
I'm in Kanto, and Ibaraki is in Kanto, too,
But I don't know if it's possible to come to Saitama,
But, well, it was the first time for me to go to Kawaguchi.
It was my first time in Kawaguchi.
I had been performing at Omiya Sonic City until now,
Kawaguchi Sogo Bunka Center Lilia Main Hall was quite new to me.
It was early.
And on June 10 and 11, I will be at the main hall of Tochigi Prefectural Culture Center in Tochigi.
Lots of Tochigi, too.
Tochigi was a good day for get-togethers, I thought.
Was it good?
That's the day when there was ramen.
Ah.
And strawberry milk and lemon milk. There was strawberry milk and lemon milk. Yes, yes.
It was delicious. It was delicious.
Our, uh, our mother is a gyoza (dumpling) mother. Our mother bought us 100 dumplings.
A hundred. She bought 100 dumplings.
They were delicious. They were delicious.
We ate a lot.
After the party, everyone asked to leave some of the food for the caterer, so they ate it after the party was over.
Also, the president of Iwashita Ginger came to the party.
Yes, Aya-chan mentioned on the radio that Iwashita's fresh ginger was delicious, and when I told her about it, she came.
Everything from his head to his shoes was bright pink.
He was a kind man. He was very kind.
Yes, and June 17 is the Tokyo Dome City Hall. All at once.
It's a repetition, isn't it?
It was something like that, wasn't it? It was like a smaller version of the big concert hall.
The venue had a different feel to it.
It was different from the previous venues.
What was that place? The venue for the big concert.
The Garden Theater. It may indeed resemble the shape of a garden theater.
It sounded different, and I think it was difficult.
It sounds cool, but it doesn't have the same sound.
It sounds cool, but it doesn't sound the same.
I started talking to Mirei about all kinds of things.
I would ask her how I should tell her when I wanted to do something like this.
We are talking about how to create the sound for each venue, now, aren't we?
Are you talking to Mirei?
I asked her how to say "boom," and she said, "Just say 'boom, boom, boom.
She gave me advice just like that.
She advised me to tell the monitor man, the person who monitors me, and the PA that I should say "boom" to him.I was advised by the monitor man to tell the PA about the "booming" sound that he was giving me.
Recently, I've been able to do a lot of things.
It's kind of cool, isn't it? Suddenly you've grown up, haven't you? I knew it.
I used to only say, "It's OK," so now I can do a lot of things.
The next concert will be held on June 18 at Chiba Ichikawa City Cultural Hall in Chiba Prefecture. Chiba Prefecture.
Hinatachan.
Hinatachan's press conference.
Live performance.
I could say the same thing about the Tokyo Dome City Hall the day before, but about the ecology.
I wasn't feeling well, so I had to take two days off from singing.
So for the first time in more than 10 years of doing this, I had to lip-synch.
So I did it.
So I was really worried about how to express myself during those two days,
The day before, I really didn't know what I was going to do, to be honest.
And then, in Chiba, I finally understood a little bit, and I think I was able to do it.
I think it's difficult to do lip-synchronization.
It's very difficult to make a lip-sync.
It is difficult.
There are not many idols who say they are lip-synching.
Usually they don't.
They don't say at live shows that they are going to lip-synch today, so I'm surprised.
But I could hear everyone's voices better because they weren't singing, so it was a lot of fun.
You performed a unit song, didn't you? On this tour.
In this tour, Mayama, Hinata, and Riko were in Decadonden,
Yuna and Kaho's promise,
Mire-chan, Aya-chan, and Cocona's united thoughts.
I was challenging Yuna to change her clothes during her intro in that dekadonden,
I had changed my clothes by the end of the intro and was ready to go out anytime,
When we took a short break, I went to drink some water and Mayama-san was there.
Mayama-san said he was taking a break, but he was drinking water like this.
But that was Taiku-san, Taiku Akasaki, right?
He wrote "Family Complex" for us.
I respected him a little and let him do his thing.
I'm really looking forward to seeing you at the next 2-Man Jep Tour.
That's right. I'm really looking forward to it.
And the next one is in Fukuoka City on June 26th.
Fukuoka City. Fukuoka Civic Auditorium, right?
Yes, I'm here. I'm here in Fukuoka.
It was the first time for me to go there.
It's been a year since I've been there.
I said it was my first time, but it wasn't.
Oh, really?
I had been there once before because I crossed over when I was going to another prefecture.
Does that count as a visit?
Yes, I did. I think so.
But I heard he bought some stuff.
Did you buy them after you got off the plane?
Or did you buy it in the airport?
It depends a lot.
My mom said she went to Fukuoka.
She said she had been there when she was little, so I had been there.
Maybe I didn't just go there.
It was a little bit like that now.
It was the first time since I was in junior high school or something that I had an ego or an awareness.
Yes, it is. It is the first time. After I joined EBICHU.
And the next one was on July 3 at Kaltz Kawasaki in Kanagawa Prefecture.
Yes. I'll be able to see it.
Gaiten live.
I don't write "Gaiten" anymore.
If it's "Gaiken", we've done three times in Tokyo.
Are you nervous about performing live in Tokyo?
Yes, I am. I was so nervous that I couldn't sleep the day before,
I stayed up until about 3:00 a.m.
Yes, I was. I'll be at Kaltz Kawasaki in Kanagawa Prefecture.
It's very smooth.
Kaltz Kawasaki is that, right?
What was it?
Semi-finals.
I started to get very nervous around here because it was the semi-finals.
I was nervous about everything, but I was more nervous.
It was the semi-finals.
I've been nervous all the time.
There are only two performances left, so we mustn't make mistakes in this show,
I was so nervous because I knew I mustn't make any mistakes here.
I did it as I was saying it.
The backstage routine was a little different on the last day,
The backstroke that we usually do with the A button and the B button was the last one,
It was the last one, so I was very nervous.
Yes, it was.
And this time, there was a song called "Summer's Here, Johnny.
We performed that song with a headset instead of a hand mic,
Each member of the group was asked to carry around their favorite summer goods,
They were allowed to move around and sing freely without any choreography,
Everyone was free to do whatever they wanted,
Everyone was free to do whatever they wanted, but the sun was on the first day or from May 5, I think.
It changed quite a bit.
It started as a joke by the staff at first,
What started out as a joke by the staff became a part of the production,
It started out as a joke by the staff, but it became a part of the production.
So, for those who came to the tour and those who saw the show.......,
Those of you who have seen the show, maybe you don't? If you have seen the show, you probably know what I am talking about,
The staff came out after "It's Summer, Johnny" and didn't say a word,
I didn't say a word or anything.
There wasn't. There really wasn't,
They were just asking me to do something reckless.
Yes, yes. The more the show went on, the more freedom we had, and the more freedom the staff had.
Yes, they would come out of nowhere.
Yes, that was the case in Fukuoka.
I'm going to go back a little bit, but in Fukuoka, the staff came out.Let me back up a little bit...Fukuoka got a staff member.
The staff came out in Fukuoka.
I wondered what was going to happen now that he came out.
I was wondering what was going to happen at the end, and then it came back for a moment with "KARUTSU,
I was wondering what was going to happen at the end,
Somehow, I realized that we were going to go to the next final with this.
It's true.
It was interesting.
You said Kineo was there, but he wasn't.
It was fun.
July 9 was at LINE CUBE Shibuya in Tokyo,
The day before yesterday.
Doesn't it feel like the day before yesterday?
Yes, it does.
Which feeling do you have now?
I think it's different for each of us.
I'm the type of person who feels the afterglow of the end of a show.
Oh, I see.
But I also feel like, suddenly,
I remember how I felt at the time, or how much fun I had,
I remember them now, like yesterday or today.
So it still feels fresh as if it was yesterday.
Now there is a story-telling session,
Why do I feel like it's already over?
You mean it feels like time has already passed?
I see.
That's right.
There are all types of people. There are all types of people here.
But LINE CUBE Shibuya is a bit different,
The AB setlist was all played in one place.
So, there are many performances,
There are many performances that I couldn't mention today,
The head of the production was Ai no Rental,
The song "Let's hold hands" was a double encore,
The song "Let's hold hands" was performed as a double encore, and so on,
There were so many things to do,
I thought it was a great opportunity for the audience to enjoy the album "Series Ebichu".
I thought it was the final show where you could enjoy the album "Series Ebichu" as well.
Yes, it was.
And I made the biggest mistake in the finals.
What is it?
You spoiled it by saying that you were going to play all the new songs.
That's right.
I did it in the first MC.
You did it.
All the things I had tried so hard not to do up to this point, I did.
After the first part, after the main part,
Then, after the main part was over.
There was one song that wasn't performed,
They said, "We're going to do an encore.
You knew we were going to do it.
I knew it, didn't I?
You were spoiling it.
We hadn't done it before.
We hadn't done it.
You didn't do it.
I told him that it was good that I had guessed.
But you guessed it, didn't you?
It was a real mistake, not scripted,
But you didn't get mad at me afterwards.
It was right after Yuno-san joined,
I remember when Yuno-san first joined the company, he would often tell the end of the story before the beginning.
It's been a while since I saw that,
I felt like it was Yuno.
That's true.
It was a lot of fun.
How was it?
I guessed it from the video.
Now to the mini-corner.
Funny and huffing and puffing off-shoots.
I'll show you the photos I took along the way, one by one.
I'm going to go quickly.
You don't have to tell me.
You don't have to say "kanben.
You don't have to say "kanben" the moment they go.
I have to go down, so I can't do it smoothly.
Let's go.
I'll start with Yuno's picture.
Here you go.
Yes, this is a picture of the set of the tour.
I took this picture at the final show of the tour at Line Cable Shibuya,
I thought it was the last time I would be on this stage,
I took a lot of pictures.
It was a cool set.
I was inspired by an artist.
Even the frames in the back were exquisite, all slightly different from each other,
I realized after the final that they were all so meticulously chosen.
I also noticed that the white table below was also a little bit different,
The staircase was not dirty or anything,
The staircase and so on are not dirty, but they are soft.
Yes, yes. It was the skill of the art director.
It was a set that was made with love.
Okay, let's go to the next picture. Nonoka.
Yes, my Dong.
Yes, this is that one.
This is a picture taken in Hokkaido, at the airport,
I went to eat ramen with Coconut,
This is the ramen I had with Coconut.
It was really delicious. I took a picture of it, didn't I?It was so delicious. I took pictures, didn't I?
I took pictures, didn't I?
I couldn't go out to eat much this time.
I went to a ramen restaurant at the airport.
We went to Ramen Dojo at the airport,
We went to a miso ramen restaurant.
Yuno and Coconut ordered miso ramen, and Nonoka had salt ramen.
I thought miso ramen might be too much for everyone, so I went with the salt ramen,
But it was really delicious. It was really tasty and different from the ramen in Tokyo.
They said it was delicious and tasty.
Hokkaido is a little bit different, isn't it? I knew it.
It was delicious.
It's ramen day today. It's kind of delicious.
Then, let's take Mayama-san's picture, please.
Here you go. This way.
Kaho-chan.
Kaho-chan, but this looks like an ordinary Kaho-chan,
Actually, this is Kaho-chan.
It's a lot of luggage.
It's the same amount of luggage as she had in the past two days.
She remembers a lot of things when we talk.
That's right. Isn't it scary to think about two days and one night?
What's so scary about that?
And you were wearing the same clothes as the two days.
Yes, I was dressed the same way for two days. The scariest thing is the amount of luggage we have, even though we've been wearing the same clothes for the past two days.
We were coming out ourselves, weren't we?
Yes, that's right. It's funny, this amount of stuff.
It was very interesting.
What do you mean?
Athletes and matressees were bringing it? I mean, it's like, "Oh, my God, what kind of athlete brings a matress?
On the other hand, Aya. I don't have a picture of her,
When Aya-chan had to run down to the kitchen for dinner, she brought only one bag.
And it was a tote bag.
I forgot a lot of things, didn't I?
So many things happened during the tour.
It was interesting.
It was interesting. It was really interesting.
It was a fun tour with a lot of things happening.
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
The 47th edition of EBICHU's Delightful and Funny Showroom is coming to an end in no time at all.
So, I would like to make an announcement.
I'll start now.
It was announced yesterday.
Please turn over slowly.
Private Shrimp Middle School x
It's been said.
I knew it.
I thought I wrote it small and made a mistake in allocating the letters.
It's called "Shiritsu Ebichu x Natali More Ebiten Q Colors Nude,
So it's a special exhibition celebrating the 10th anniversary of Ebichu's major debut.
It will be held in Tokyo from Friday, August 19 to September 4.
The exhibition will be held at Towerboard in Tokyo from Friday, August 19 to September 4.
Osaka is at Aveeno.
Please see the website for details.
Then we will go to the next court.
Nonaka-san, do you say yourself?
My first birthday solo concert, my first walk with Nonaka Maru and my first walk with my dog.
It will take place on the day of my birthday, August 25.
Congratulations.
I'm nervous, but I'm thinking a lot right now, so please come and play.
Please do.
Yes, and.
And I'll be there.
It was announced yesterday.
The role of "Private Ebichu",
I'm sorry, it's small.
Private Shrimps,
We Sing Up Popular Tue On The Stage, entitled,
Chūon 2022
This is a mid-tone.
It's a mid-tone.
On Saturday, September 24 and Sunday, September 25, 2022.
The venue is Chichibu Muse Park Outdoor Stage.
We are going to do Chūon again this year.
The sexy selection process started at 19:00 yesterday,
We look forward to seeing you there.
Yes, please do.
And now, I will make my announcement.
Today, at 24:59,
I'll be appearing on a program called "There's someone I'd like you to meet, Audrey-san.
I will be appearing in a program called
Yes, please come in.
I appeared in this program when I was 5 and 7 years old,
I said I wanted to be an idol, and I became an idol and went back to being an idol,
Please watch the show.
Please watch the show. It is distributed in various places,
Please watch it today.
Today's show is on Chukyo TV.
It will be broadcast on July 14,
I hope you enjoy it as much as I do.
I want to see it.
Okay, so here it is,
I would like to announce the final luncheon of Ebichu.
Fifth place, Mr. Oya.
Thank you very much.
Fourth place, Mr. Monta.
In third place, Kohei Hokkaido-san.Third place, Kouping Hokkaido.
Thank you very much.
Second place, Chinatsu.
First place, Ms. Tamamii.
Thank you very much.
That concludes the 47th edition of Ebichu's Delightful and Funny Showroom.
And an important announcement.
The next broadcast will be on Wednesday, August 3rd at 8:00.
Just before Famien, right?
That's right.
And please look forward to it.
This distribution will also include the review meeting that will take place after this broadcast,
Please check it out.
We will end the streaming once, but we will resume it right after a little while,
Please stay tuned.
Please stay tuned. If there is anything you would like to tell us in the review session, please leave a comment,
If you have anything you would like to tell us in the review session, please leave a comment.
Please do.
That's all for now, this is Private Shrimp Middle School.
Bye bye.
Have a good New Year's.
Oh, that's right. I gave it to you again.
The next broadcast will be on Wednesday, August 3.
See you soon.
Thanks for watching!
Thanks for your time.
You have a great voice.
Thank you very much for your time.
Thank you for your hard work.
Mayama-san, it's been a while
How have you two grown?
Yes, they have
But...
I don't know...
You were moving along calmly, weren't you?
I thought I made a mistake in allocating the time at the end.
I didn't know how to distribute the time, so I made a mistake.
I made a mistake.
Not at all.
That was good.
Nonaka did a super follow-up.
He was the devil of follow-ups.
Really?
He followed up on everything we couldn't remember.
He followed up on everything.
Nonaka was amazing at the backstage.
That was great.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure it's a peculiar habit to say that.
How was Mr. Koho?
When we started talking about the first tour...
I thought I talked a little too much.
It turned into a true reflection session.
What's that?
But, you know... it's just... you know...
I can't believe there were so many episodes in each show.
If I were to bias one of them, I'd feel sorry for the people who went.
So I think you've done a really good job of organizing the episodes.
I think they got that part right.
I'm going to wrestle hard.
Mr. Kokuma
We had a lot of time to talk today, so...
We couldn't do it this time.
We'll see you next time for the Fami-en project.
Yes, next time.
I'll tell you about it next time.
You'll be the MC next time?
Will you be MC next time?
No, I'll try my best to get revenge when I'm allowed to MC again.
Well then, Mr. Kokuma, please close the show.
Thank you very much.
Oh, no!
You're good!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you for watching